{
  "questionSet2": [
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "What is the HTML element used to display a paragraph?",
      "correctAnswer": "<p>",
      "choices": ["<span>", "<h1>", "<p>", "<br>"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "To change the family of a text's font, what style attribute should you use to do this?",
      "correctAnswer": "font-family",
      "choices": ["color", "font-family", "font-size", "text-align"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "What is the HTML element used a section of an HTML page? Type your answer like: <tagname>?",
      "correctAnswer": "<div>",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "If you wanted to add a internal style or script onto an HTML page, the tags should be in what HTML element? Type your answer like: <tagname>",
      "correctAnswer": "<head>",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "If you want to include a checkbox using <form>, the input type you should use is radio. True or False?",
      "correctAnswer": "false",
      "choices": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "<script> is used to link a external Javascript file to the HTML file. True or False?",
      "correctAnswer": "true",
      "choices": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "Which of the following is NOT an input type for a form input?",
      "correctAnswer": "video",
      "choices": ["checkbox", "text", "button", "video"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "What does CSS stand for?",
      "correctAnswer": "Cascading Style Sheets",
      "choices": ["Casual Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Cascading Style Styles", "Cascading Language Style"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "fill_in_blank",
      "questionText": "The _____ property changes the horizontal alignment of a text.",
      "correctAnswer": "text-align",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "fill_in_blank",
      "questionText": "What HTML attribute completes this syntax: <a ____='www.Google.com/'>?",
      "correctAnswer": "href",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "narrative",
      "questionText": "You are working on a Javascript file on your preferred web application tool. You want to create a constant variable within the script. What would you use to declare this, const or var?",
      "correctAnswer": "const",
      "choices": ["const", "var"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "Which of the following is NOT a way to define functions?",
      "correctAnswer": "function syntax",
      "choices": ["function expression", "function declaration", "arrow syntax", "function syntax"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "What HTML element is used to make an ordered list? Type your answer like: <tagname>",
      "correctAnswer": "<ol>",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "To change the color of a button using bootstrap, you would have to change btn-btn-primary to btn-btn-success in the code. True or False?",
      "correctAnswer": "true",
      "choices": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "true_false",
      "questionText": "<iframe> is one of the ways you can include a video onto an HTML page. True or False?",
      "correctAnswer": "true",
      "choices": ["true", "false"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "fill_in_blank",
      "questionText": "The ______ attribute shows where the image to be displayed is located",
      "correctAnswer": "src",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "Which of the following is an class selector for CSS?",
      "correctAnswer": ".h1",
      "choices": ["h1", ".h1", "*", "#h1"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "multiple_choice",
      "questionText": "When using responsive design in CSS, what tag should you use to control the viewport?",
      "correctAnswer": "<meta>",
      "choices": ["<link>", "<script>", "<meta>", "<style>"]
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "What is the acronym used for allowing Javascript objects to be used in text format?",
      "correctAnswer": "JSON",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    },
    {
      "questionType": "text_input",
      "questionText": "What HTML element is used to access an external CSS file? Type your answer like: <tagname>",
      "correctAnswer": "<link>",
      "answerFieldId": "answer_to_question"
    } 
  ]
}
